etransporter.info 2009-05-18

# Free Proxy, Free Proxy Server, Free Anonymous Surfing with bookmarks - eTransporter.info

We are committed to respecting your privacy and recognize your need for appropriate protection and management of personally identifiable information you share with us (any information by which you can be identified, such as name, address, and telephone number). That is why etransporter.info has established this privacy policy, so that you can understand the care which we intend to treat your information.

Almost of browers utilizes "[cookies](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTP_cookie)" so that we can better serve you with more tailored information when you return to our site. Cookies are identifiers which a web site can send to your browser to keep on your computer to faciliate your next visit to this proxy. You can set your browser to notify you when you are sent a cookie, giving you the change to decide wherever or not to accept it. The information we collect and anylyze is used to improve our service to you.

To protect your privacy, we have adopted the following principles:

### Information

We want to give you information about our privacy policy and assure you that we take reasonable steps to see that it is followed with our service.

### Choice

There are times when we may collect your personal information from you. It is our intend to inform you before we do that and to tell you what we intend to do with information. You will have the option not to privide the information, and in the future you will able to "opt out" of certain uses of the information. If you choose not to provide the information we request, you can still visit most of etransporter.info proxy, but you may unable to access to certain options, offers and services.

### Accuracy

We do our best to maintain the accuracy of personal information you supply to us; we are working on tools that will allow you review and update your information in the future.

### Security

We will take appropriate steps to protect the information you share with us from unauthorized access or disclosure.

Last Updated: November, 05 2007 12:00 P.M GMT.
